{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Lawn Dethatching Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/62289/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":62289,"taskName":"Lawn Care - Dethatching","taskDescription":"Dethatch or Power Rake a Lawn","xmTaskDescriptor":"Lawn Dethatching Services","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":null,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"thatch, dethatch, powerraking, powerrake, raking, rake","textMessagingName":"Dethatch/PowerRake","rolloverLongDesc":"Lawn thatch removal using dethatching rakes or power rakes to ensure a healthier lawn.","rolloverShortDesc":"Lawn Dethatching and Power Raking","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors for Lawn Dethatching and Power Raking.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Lawn Dethatching \u0026 Power Raking Services \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Thatch Removal","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":48,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Lawn Dethatching","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Lawn Care - Dethatching","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Thatch Removal Project","urlName":"Lawn-Dethatching","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Lawn Dethatching and Power Raking Services in \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"lawn, thatch, dethatch, grass, powerraking, powerrake, raking, rake, power raking, power rake","emcCategoryOid":-12047,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":8733,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/62289/":{"taskOID":62289,"originalTaskOID":62289,"setID":8733,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6356,"questionDisplayText":"Lawn area in square feet","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the square footage of your lawn?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20410,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1,000 (Small)","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1,000 (Small)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20411,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1,000 - 3,000 (Medium)","answerDisplayText":"1,000 - 3,000 (Medium)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20412,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3,000 - 10,000 (Large)","answerDisplayText":"3,000 - 10,000 (Large)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20413,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"10,000 - 20,000 (Very large)","answerDisplayText":"10,000 - 20,000 (Very large)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20414,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 20,000 (1/2 Acre +)","answerDisplayText":"More than 20,000 (1/2 Acre +)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5213,"questionDisplayText":"Other Services","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What other services are you interested in? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20402,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Lawn aeration","answerDisplayText":"Lawn aeration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8188,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Weed control","answerDisplayText":"Weed control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20404,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Fertilization","answerDisplayText":"Fertilization","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20400,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Leaf Removal","answerDisplayText":"Leaf Removal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202005,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"General yard clean up","answerDisplayText":"General yard clean up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4271,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"None","answerDisplayText":"None","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6360,"questionDisplayText":"Recurring Service Requested","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Will this request be a recurring service?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20426,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20427,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6356,"questionDisplayText":"Lawn area in square feet","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the square footage of your lawn?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20410,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1,000 (Small)","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1,000 (Small)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20411,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1,000 - 3,000 (Medium)","answerDisplayText":"1,000 - 3,000 (Medium)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20412,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3,000 - 10,000 (Large)","answerDisplayText":"3,000 - 10,000 (Large)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20413,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"10,000 - 20,000 (Very large)","answerDisplayText":"10,000 - 20,000 (Very large)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20414,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 20,000 (1/2 Acre +)","answerDisplayText":"More than 20,000 (1/2 Acre +)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20410,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1,000 (Small)","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1,000 (Small)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20411,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1,000 - 3,000 (Medium)","answerDisplayText":"1,000 - 3,000 (Medium)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20412,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3,000 - 10,000 (Large)","answerDisplayText":"3,000 - 10,000 (Large)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20413,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"10,000 - 20,000 (Very large)","answerDisplayText":"10,000 - 20,000 (Very large)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20414,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 20,000 (1/2 Acre +)","answerDisplayText":"More than 20,000 (1/2 Acre +)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5213,"questionDisplayText":"Other Services","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What other services are you interested in? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20402,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Lawn aeration","answerDisplayText":"Lawn aeration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8188,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Weed control","answerDisplayText":"Weed control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20404,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Fertilization","answerDisplayText":"Fertilization","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20400,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Leaf Removal","answerDisplayText":"Leaf Removal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202005,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"General yard clean up","answerDisplayText":"General yard clean up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4271,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"None","answerDisplayText":"None","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20402,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Lawn aeration","answerDisplayText":"Lawn aeration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8188,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Weed control","answerDisplayText":"Weed control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20404,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Fertilization","answerDisplayText":"Fertilization","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20400,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Leaf Removal","answerDisplayText":"Leaf Removal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202005,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"General yard clean up","answerDisplayText":"General yard clean up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4271,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"None","answerDisplayText":"None","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6360,"questionDisplayText":"Recurring Service Requested","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Will this request be a recurring service?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20426,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20427,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20426,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20427,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}